<DialogueTree xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/xen-42/outer-wilds-new-horizons/main/NewHorizons/Schemas/dialogue_schema.xsd">
	<NameField>Fixxion</NameField>

	<DialogueNode>
		<Name></Name>
		<EntryCondition>DEFAULT</EntryCondition>
		<Dialogue>
			<Page>Welcome to my assortment of planets, I hope you enjoy discovering their secrets!</Page>
			<Page>You can use the black holes around us to warp to any planet you want.</Page>
			<Page>Theres a signal on the in front of each of them indicating which planet is linked to that Black Hole.</Page>
			<Page>Each black hole is marked by a projection in front of it that tells you where it will take you to.</Page>
			<Page>What planet do you want to explore first?</Page>
		</Dialogue>

		<DialogueOptionsList>
			<DialogueOption>
				<Text><![CDATA[<b>Jotunn</b>]]></Text>
				<DialogueTarget>1</DialogueTarget>
			</DialogueOption>
			<DialogueOption>
				<Text><![CDATA[<b>Gaia</b>]]></Text>
				<DialogueTarget>7</DialogueTarget>
			</DialogueOption>
			<DialogueOption>
				<Text><![CDATA[<b>Midas</b>]]></Text>
				<DialogueTarget>2</DialogueTarget>
			</DialogueOption>
			<DialogueOption>
				<Text><![CDATA[<b>Surtr</b>]]></Text>
				<DialogueTarget>8</DialogueTarget>
			</DialogueOption>
			<DialogueOption>
				<Text><![CDATA[<b>The Lair</b>]]></Text>
				<DialogueTarget>3</DialogueTarget>
			</DialogueOption>
			<DialogueOption>
				<Text>Who the F*** are you?!</Text>
				<DialogueTarget>6</DialogueTarget>
			</DialogueOption>
		</DialogueOptionsList>
	</DialogueNode>
	
	<DialogueNode>
		<Name>1</Name>
		<Dialogue>
			<Page>It's always a good idea to start from the bottom.</Page>
			<Page>Jotunn is a very cold planet making hard to live on and quite dark.</Page>
			<Page>Gin, a good friend of mine, lives there. He enjoys it, but I can't understand why...</Page>
			<Page>Enter into the black hole to my left when you feel ready and it'll warp you there.</Page>
			<Page>Good luck!</Page>
		</Dialogue>
	</DialogueNode>

	<DialogueNode>
		<Name>2</Name>
		<Dialogue>
			<Page>Midas is a beautiful planet filled with molten gold.</Page>
			<Page>(It's actually gold-tinted water, but I shouldn't be telling you that...)</Page>
			<Page>Now... good luck! You will need it, as this one is a bit scarier than Gaia.</Page>
		</Dialogue>
	</DialogueNode>
	
	<DialogueNode>
		<Name>8</Name>
		<Dialogue>
			<Page>Surtr is not a great planet to visit, as it's pretty deadly.</Page>
		    	<Page>It's suffocating over there, which is the opposite of <![CDATA[<b>"Jotunn"</b>]]>. Be careful around the lava, too!</Page>
			<Page>I'm linked to a mnemonic statue, just like you! Seeing you wake up here again and again is making me starting to like you. UwU</Page>
		    	<Page>Ready? Then use the black hole next to the campfire and you'll get to Surtr in no time.</Page>
		</Dialogue>
	</DialogueNode>
		
	<DialogueNode>
		<Name>7</Name>
		<Dialogue>
			<Page>Have you already explored <![CDATA[<b>"Jotunn"</b>]]>?</Page>
		    	<Page>I don't actually care... Gaia is a nice place. It's really pretty and full of nature and beauty.</Page>
		    	<Page>Go ahead! Please enjoy your visit.</Page>
			<Page>Feel free to use the black hole next to Jotunn's.</Page>
		</Dialogue>
	</DialogueNode>
		
	<DialogueNode>
		<Name>3</Name>
		<Dialogue>
			<Page>OHHHHH Really? Do you really want to go to <![CDATA[<b>"The Lair"</b>]]>?</Page>
		</Dialogue>
		

	 <DialogueOptionsList>
		<DialogueOption>
			<Text>Huh... Not really...</Text>
			<DialogueTarget>4</DialogueTarget>
		</DialogueOption>
		<DialogueOption>
			<Text>Don't underestimate me, I can handle it!</Text>
			<DialogueTarget>5</DialogueTarget>
		</DialogueOption>
	 </DialogueOptionsList>
	</DialogueNode>

	<DialogueNode>
		<Name>6</Name>
		<Dialogue>
			<Page>First of all, don't talk to me like that.</Page>
			<Page>But... Hi! I'm the mod's creator's spiritual representation in Outer Wilds.</Page>
			<Page>His name is Fixxion, and you can contact him many different ways.</Page>
			<Page>You can always contact him through the Official Outer Wilds Modding Discord Server to make suggestions. I'm sure he will listen.</Page>
			<Page>He spends most of his time on Youtube as <![CDATA[<b>"Fixxion's Lair"</b>]]>, where he makes Spanish videogame content. Especially Outer Wilds content.</Page>
			<Page>Be sure to check him out if you are interested!</Page>
		</Dialogue>
	</DialogueNode>

	<DialogueNode>
		<Name>4</Name>
		<Dialogue>
			<Page>Wise choice. Talk to me again before you visit the other planets.</Page>
		</Dialogue>
	</DialogueNode>

	<DialogueNode>
		<Name>5</Name>
		<Dialogue>
			<Page>HAHAHAHA! I like your spirit! Just make sure you don't... well... you will find out yourself.</Page>
			<Page>See ya! Or not... Just try not to make a lot of noise.</Page>
		</Dialogue>
	</DialogueNode>
	
</DialogueTree>